早安  猛虎
Good morning,tiger.
我在帮你准备丰盛的早餐
I'm making you a big breakfast,
好让你晚上能够"精力旺盛"
so you can keep up your strength for tonight.
让我欲仙欲死  让我一夜大肚
You're gonna get me good and pregnant.
我今早不知何去何从  我失业了
I've got nowhere to go this morning. I'm unemployed.
我不知道人生该怎么办才好
I don't know what I'm gonna do with my life.
很好  我没有性趣了
Well,I just lost my erection.
不  我是说  我该去干些什么呢
No,I mean,what am I supposed to do with myself?
你应该要找寻生命中的热情
You're supposed to find your passion in life.
你现在可以做任何你想做的事
You can be whatever you want to be now.
很刺激的
It's exciting.
是啊  但是也太突然了
Yeah,but it's all so overwhelming.
我不知道要从何开始
I don't know where to start.
等一下  我可以帮你
Wait a second. I can help you with this.
你只要按部就班就行了
You just need to be organized.
我们可以列出你的资历
We can make a list of your qualifications..
然后按行业将工作岗位分类
and categorize jobs by industry.
可以用档案夹  文档
There could be folders and files..
嘿  现在是你强迫症般热爱整理
Hey,this is where your hyperorganized
惹人烦的性格派上用场的时候了
painintheass stuff pays off.
我知道
I know!
我又有性趣了
My erection is back!
《老友记》  第九季 第11集  瑞秋复工
Friends S09E11 The One Where Rachael Goes Back to Work
谢谢
Thank you.
菲比  你有没有
Phoebe,have you ever been
被饥饿的意大利人咬过呢
bitten by a hungry Italian?
我很抱歉  只是我最近手头有点紧
I'm sorry. It's just,I'm a little short on cash.
如果你愿意  我可以借你一些钱
If you want,I could loan you some money.
不  我已经得过教训
Oh,no. no. I learned
千万别跟朋友借钱
never to borrow money from friends.
理查德·德莱弗斯（奥斯卡影帝）
That's why Richard Dreyfuss
和我就是因为那个才绝交的
and I don't speak anymore.
嘿  要不要这样
Hey,how about this?
来我们剧组当临时演员
Wanna be an extra on my show?
可以吗  当然
You could do that?  Yeah
薪水算不错
The pay's pretty good,
而且你想做多久都可以
and you could do it for as long as you need.
噢  我的天  我要上电视了
Oh,my God. I'm gonna be on TV!
好了  现在
Okay,now..
我必须告诉你  上电视
I gotta tell you,being on TV isn't
并不像你想像的那样光鲜有趣
as glamorous and exciting as you think.
是吗
Really?
不  是比那更棒
No,it is awesomer.
嗨  你们好
Hey,guys.
为什么你们穿的这么正式
Why are you all dressed up?
瑞秋和我要带艾玛去罗夫罗兰
Rach and I are bringing Emma to Ralph Lauren today
跟大家见面
to introduce her to everyone.
她看起来可爱吧
Doesn't she look cute?
确实很可爱
She sure does.
为什么要贴那个
Why does she have a
粉红色的蝴蝶结在她头上呢
pink bow taped to her head?
因为如果再有人说
Because if one more person says,
"真是个可爱的小男生"
"What a cute little boy"..
我会用车子的天线鞭打他们
I'm gonna whip them with a car antenna.
我想她会是办公室里面最时髦的
I think she's gonna be the hit of the office.
是啊  她一定会比那些
Yeah,she's gonna be hotter than
村妇上衣跟A字裙时髦多了
peasant blouses and Aline skirts.
我可以戴个蓝色的蝴蝶结吗
Can I get a blue bow?
好了  我看过很多的招聘广告
Okay. I have looked through a bunch of career guides..
拷贝好  并划线标示出重要讯息
photocopied and highlighted key passages..
然后以字母分类归档
and put them into alphabetical folders,
给你充分的信息  好让你做决定
so you can make an informed decision.
我在里面多久了
How long was I in there?
好了  我们先从A开始  广告业
Okay,let's start with the A's. Advertising.
等一下  广告  真是个好主意
Wait. Advertising,that's a great idea.
你不想要听别的了吗
Don't you wanna look through the rest?
我想我不用听别的了
I don't think I have to hear the rest.
广告最适合了
Advertising makes perfect sense.
很抱歉浪费你这么多时间
Sorry you had to waste all this time.
你是说花8小时
You call eight hours alone
加上制作标签是浪费时间
with my label maker wasted time?
现在可以用上我的碎纸机了
Now I'll get to use my shredder!
我也可以写广告语的
I mean,I could write slogans.
能有多难呢 是不是
How hard could it be,right?
"乳酪  可以咬的牛奶"
"Cheese. It's milk that you chew."
"饼干  乳酪的良伴"
"Crackers. Because your cheese needs a buddy."
"葡萄  西瓜太大  葡萄可一口塞下"
"A grape. Because who can get a watermelon in your mouth?"
我想到一个
I got one.
"袜子
"Socks.
您家人的脚  值得享受最好的"
Because your family's feet deserve the best."
亲爱的  让专业的人说好吗
Honey,leave it to the pros.
我认识一个在广告业工作的人
I actually know someone in advertising.
我跟他从小玩到大
I grew up with a guy
现在他是一家大广告公司的副总
who is a vice president at a big agency.
或许我可以请他跟你谈谈
Maybe I can get him to meet you.
把电话给我
Give me the phone.
"电话  让你与有电话的人更贴近"
"The phone. Bringing you closer to people who have phones."
"婚姻  不是每个人都适合的"
"Marriage. It's not for everybody."
真不错
That went well.
几乎所有人都知道她是个女孩
Almost everybody knew that she was a girl.
是啊  你揍了那个错认为是男孩的家伙后
Yeah,after you punched that one guy who got it wrong,
消息很快传开了
word spread.
我要进去我办公室拿点东西
I'm just gonna go in my office and pick up some stuff.
你他妈是谁  你他妈又是谁
Who the hell are you?  Who the hell are you?
我是这间办公室的主人
I'm the hell person whose office this is.
说的好  瑞秋
Good one,Rach.
我是加文·米奇
I'm Gavin Mitchell,
接下来要接替你工作的人
the person who's taking over your job.
什么
Excuse me?
你的宝宝真可爱
Your baby's so cute.
但是为什么
But why would you
在男孩头上贴个粉红色蝴蝶结呢
put a pink bow on a boy?
嘿  乔伊  看看我
Hey,Joey. Look at me.
我是护士耶
I'm a nurse.
是啊  真是呢
Yes,you are.
我想该是擦海棉澡的时候了
I think it might be time for my sponge bath.
对不起  我太习惯泡临时演员了
Sorry,I'm just so used to hitting on the extras.
你很期待出场吗
So are you excited about your scene?
是啊  但是我有点紧张
Yeah,but I'm a little nervous.
放轻松  别紧张  没事的
Relax. Don't be. You will be fine.
他们可能只会要你站在后面
They'll probably just make you stand in the background.
好了  好了
OK. OK. OK
你  站这里  过来  这里  好的
You. Here,come here. Here.  OK
你拿着这个托盘  站在黄线这里
Take this tray,stand on this yellow mark.
听到"开拍"就开始移动
You're gonna move on "action."
走向手术台  停在蓝线那边
Walk over to the operating table,stop on the blue mark
然后把托盘放下
and put the tray down.
别走太快
Don't walk too fast.
但是也别太慢
But don't dawdle.
好吧  到底是怎样
Okay. Now,what?
开拍
And,action!
停  停
Cut! Cut.
我很抱歉  我只是有点紧张
I'm sorry. I'm just a little nervous.
那就别紧张
Well,don't be.
好吧  你的话真"有用"
Okay,that helps.
开拍
And,action!
停
Cut!
那个  别担心  菲比
You know what? Don't worry about it,Phoebe.
我通常也要3次才能拍成功
It usually takes me three takes too.
好啦  是8次
All right,eight.
开拍
And,action!
那你对于广告还有其他问题吗
So do you have any other questions about advertising?
没有  但是让我表演一下我的专长
No. But let me show you what I can do.
百吉饼和甜甜圈
"Bagels and doughnuts.
任何心情都适合吃的圆圈圈
Round food for every mood."
莫妮卡警告过我  你可能会这样做
Monica warned me you might do that.
我想我们公司可能有个适合你的职务
I think we might have something for you at the agency.
真的吗  太好了
Really? That's great.
有个不付薪水的实习职位
It's an unpaid internship.
真好笑  当你说"不付薪水"的时候
That's funny. When you said "unpaid,"
听起来好像是"不给钱"的意思
it sounded like you said "unpaid."
别这样  莫妮卡有份很不错的工作
Come on,now. Monica has a good job.
又不是说你要养家糊口
It's not like you have a family to support.
事实上  我们正想生个孩子
Actually,we're trying.
我不认为莫妮卡想要延期
I don't think Monica is gonna want to postpone it.
我们原打算今晚做爱的
We're supposed to have sex tonight.
事实上  她现在或许就在家
Actually,she's probably at home,
一丝不挂的
naked right now.
如果没有人阻止我  我会一直说话
I tend to keep talking till somebody stops me.
我可以想像她在床上的样子  停
I can just picture her on the bed.  Stop!
好吧
OK.
等等
Wait a minute.
你说要接替我的工作是什么意思
What do you mean you're taking over my job?
你休产假的时候
While you were on your baby vacation,
你的工作是我在做的
I was doing your job.
假期  我对假期的定义可不包括
A vacation? My idea of a vacation does not involve..
让什么东西吸我的乳房  吸到破皮
something sucking on my nipples until they are raw.
很显然  你从未去过天堂度假岛
Clearly,you've never been to Sandals Paradise lsland.
好了  别让你自己太舒服
All right. Don't get too comfortable there,
因为我两个星期之后就回来了
because I'm back in two weeks.
我要一切回归原状
I want everything back the way it was.
我实在不太满意
I can't say I care too much
你重新摆设我办公室的方式
for the way you've rearranged my office.
我也实在不太满意你带进来的臭味
I can't say I care too much for that smell you've brought in.
你说什么
Excuse me?
瑞秋  我们面临"棕色警报状况"
Rach,we have a code brown situation.
亲爱的  可以拜托你帮我处理一下吗
Honey,could you please take care of it for me?
好吧  但是有时候你也该处理一次
All right,but you're gonna have to do one sometime.
让我把话说清楚
Let me just get this straight.
我去生个小孩
So I go have a baby,
然后他们派一个人过来接我的工作
and they send some guy in to do my job?
本来说要关闭整个罗夫罗兰的
Well,there was talk of shutting down Ralph Lauren altogether.
好了  你真是个不要脸的临时工
Okay. Right. You're very cheeky for a temp.
我不是临时工
I'm not a temp.
我是从别的部门调过来的
I was transferred here from another department.
是什么部门呢  混蛋部门吗
And what department was that? The jerk department?
他们并没有告诉我  你反应是如此快
They didn't tell me about your quick wit.
那他们有没有告诉你
Well,did they mention
我是橡胶  你是胶水吗
that I'm rubber and you're glue?
加文  罗夫很喜欢你的创意
Gavin,Ralph loved your ideas.
嗨  泽纳先生
Hi,Mr. Zelner.
瑞秋  我想你见过加文了
Rachel. I see you've met Gavin.
当你离开的时候
When you left us,
我们都不知道该怎么办
we weren't sure what we were gonna do.
但是  加文拯救了我们  超级加文
But then,Gavin to the rescue. Super Gavin.
噢  太好了  太好了
Well,that's great. that's great.
那么  超级加文  当我回来以后
So now,Super Gavin,when I come back..
你计划要飞到哪去呢
where do you plan on flying off to?
全看泽纳先生的意思
That's up to Mr. Zelner.
我相信他会做出正确的决定
I'm sure he'll make the right decision.
超级马屁精
Super asskissing power.
对了  你什么时候回来呢
Incidentally,when are you coming back?
今天
Today.
你刚刚说两星期后
You said two weeks.
不  我是说今天
No,I said today.
看吧  身为超级英雄
See,for a superhero,
听话能力有点差劲哦
not so much with the listening.
他怎么说呢
So,what'd he say?
他有时候有点粗暴
He can be a little rough around the edges..
所以我打算将他使用
so I'm gonna replace a word
频率很高的一个脏字换成"小狗"
he used a lot with the word "puppy."
他说  如果你的"小狗"朋友
So he said,"If your puppy friend
不能"小狗"演好她的角色
doesn't get her puppy act together..
我将会"小狗"般地开除她
I am gonna fire her motherpuppy ass."
我很抱歉  我办不到
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
我不是演员的料
I'm just not an actor.
没错  你不是演员  你是护士
That's right. You're not. You're a nurse.
你是拿托盘的护士  别  乔伊
You're Nurse With Tray.  No,Joey..
不  拿托盘的护士不认识乔伊的
No, no. Nurse With Tray doesn't know Joey.
她没有时间交朋友
She has no time for friends.
她进去手术室
She gets in that operating room
把托盘交给医生
and she carries that tray to the doctor..
因为如果她不这样做  会死人的
because if she doesn't,people die.
谁会死
Who dies?
戴眼罩的男人
Man With Eye Patch!
现在你过去做好你的工作
Now,you get in there,and you do your job.
遵命  医生  好的
Yes,doctor. OK
好了  我们再试一次
Okay,let's try this one more time.
撑着点  戴眼罩的男人
Hang in there,Man With Eye Patch.
你的托盘来了
Your tray is coming.
开拍
And,action.
太棒了  我办到了  我搞定了
Yes,I did it! I nailed it!
接下来是什么呢
What's next?
继续后面的剧情
The rest of the scene.
好吧  大家  从头开始
Okay,from the top,people.
听着  计划有变
Listen,sudden change of plans.
我的产假刚刚结束了
My maternity leave just ended.
他们说如果我不今天回去工作
They said if I didn't come back today,
他们就要开除我
they'd fire me.
什么 那是非法的
What? No,that's illegal.
我要马上通知工会  他们不...
I'll have the Labor Department here so fast,they won't..
好了  冷静点  诺玛蕾（工会创建者）
All right,calm down,Norma Rae.
他们并没有真的那样说
They didn't actually say that.
我只是害怕如果不现在回去
I'm just afraid if I don't come back now,
那个男的会把我挤掉
this guy will try and squeeze me out.
那艾玛怎么办呢
But what about Emma?
我们还没有找到保姆
I mean,we don't have a nanny.
我知道  我们只好今晚再想办法了
I know. We're just gonna have to figure out a plan tonight.
今天你可以先照顾她吗
Can you please just take care of her for today?
当然  只要把你的乳房给我
Absolutely. Just give me your breasts,
我们马上就走
and we'll be on our way.
别这样  我不知道还能怎么办
Come on. I don't know what else to do.
好啦  好啦
Fine. Fine.
我们会很开心的  不是吗
We'll have fun,won't we?
是的  我们会  是的  我们
Yes,we will. Yes,we..
罗斯
Ross.
你好漂亮
You're pretty.
不管我决定要做什么
Whatever I decide to do,
我都得从基层做起
I'm gonna be starting a new career from scratch.
得很长一段时间后才能活得滋润些
It's gonna be a while before I make a living at it.
或许现在不是生小孩的好时机
Maybe now's not the right time to be starting a family.
所以你要跟莫妮卡说
So you have to tell Monica
你现在不想要生小孩
you don't want to have a baby right now?
是啊
Yeah.
永别了
Goodbye.
好了  造人时间  裤子脱掉  宾
Okay,it's baby time. Pants off,Bing.
没看到你也在  盖勒
Didn't see you there,Geller.
罗斯在这里  所以
Ross is here,so..
我真的希望  可以跟你们待在一起
And I was really hoping that maybe I could hang out.
你们想做什么呢
You know,what do you feel like doing?
我们想要做爱
Well,we're gonna have sex.
我倒是不太想做爱
I don't feel like having sex.
或许  我不知道
Maybe.. I don't know.
或许我们可以一起看电影什么的
Maybe we can watch a movie or something.
我就直说了吧
Let me put it this way:
不管你在不在  我们都要做爱
We're having sex whether you're here or not.
裤子脱掉  宾
Pants off,Bing.
听着  现在既然我回来了
All right. Now that I'm back,
何不向我报告一下
why don't you just fill me in
你都干了些什么
on what you've been up to.
嗯  我把你超级男孩的屏保改了
Well,I've changed your screen saver from that picture of NSYNC.
嘿  我离开时  他们可是很受欢迎的
Hey,they were popular when I left.
但我主要忙于准备
Mostly I've just been working on
明天的一个重要报告展示
this big presentation for tomorrow.
我应该要参与  向我说明一下吧
I should be involved in that,so get me up to speed.
那得花上好几个星期
That'll take weeks.
你不如就让我负责那个报告吧
Why don't you just let me take care of the presentation.
不  我知道你在玩什么花样  好吗
No. I see what you're doing here,all right?
听着  这是我的工作  老兄
Listen, this is my job,buddy.
我已经做了五年了  我知道一切流程
I've had it for five years,and I know how it works.
所以赶快向我汇报说明  好
So why don't you just catch me up.  Fine.
天啊
Oh,God.
你把我椅子的高度完全变了
You've totally messed with the back support on my chair.
你是怎么弄的
How do you fix this?
你已经在这里五年了
You've been here five years.
你自己想吧  很好  我自己来
You figure it out.  Fine,I will.
好了  开始汇报吧
All right,fill me in.
你有没有蓝色的领带配我的衣服
Do you have a blue tie that would go with this?
艾玛吐奶到我的领带上
Emma spit up on mine.
有啊  但等我找到工作时要还给我
Yeah,but you have to give it back if I get a job.
当然  到那时候  领带已经被淘汰了
Of course,by that time, future ties will be obsolete..
而我们都将穿起银色的连身装
and we'll all be wearing silver jumpsuits.
早安  爱人
Hey,good morning,lover.
我得说  经过昨夜的激战
I gotta say,after last night,
我的双腿还在发软
I'm a little weak in the knees.
麻烦你  每次走进来的时候
Here's an idea. You walk into a room,
先快速看一下四周吧
take a quick scan.
抱歉
Sorry.
但是我有点觉得
But I kind of have this feeling
我们昨晚造人成功了
that we may have made a baby last night.
噢  天  我必须告诉你一件事
Oh,God,I have to tell you something.
你没有怀孕
You're not pregnant.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
嗯  能让你受精的那件事
Well,that thing that I have to do to make a baby?
我装的
I faked it.
什么  你装的
What? You faked it?
你知道吗
You know what?
我不需要领带了
I don't need a tie.
我是说  领子开着比较好  不是吗
I mean,it's better open collar,you know?
比较轻松自在
It's more casual.
乔伊  听着  我办不到
Joey. Listen,I can't do this.
简直是毫无道理
It doesn't make any sense.
昨天我是护士  然后今天我是服务生
Yesterday I was a nurse,and today I'm a waitress at a cafe?
有时候我们会用相同的临时演员
Sometimes we use the same extras
扮演不同的角色  没关系的
for different parts. It's okay.
是有关系的
Well,it's not okay,
因为昨天我扮演护士  演的相当好
because I gave a very memorable performance as the nurse.
然后现在突然间  我变成服务生
And now,suddenly,I'm the waitress?
我的影迷们会混淆的
That's gonna confuse my fans.
嗯  或许你是护士
Well,maybe you are a nurse..
但是你也兼职当服务生
but you moonlight as a waitress.
因为我是抚养两个小孩的单亲妈妈
Because I'm a single mother supporting my two children.
没错
Nice.
等一下
Wait a minute.
德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
Dr. Drake Ramoray
跟我在同间医院工作
and I work at the same hospital.
我不用过来跟他打招呼吗
Wouldn't I come say hi to him?
不  不  你跟德雷克吵架了
No. No,see,you and Drake are having a fight.
吵什么
About what?
他跟你上过床
He slept with you..
但是他再也没有打电话给你
And then never called you.
而我只想帮大卫和贝琪找个新爸爸
And I just wanted a new daddy for Davey and Becky.
好了  好了  从头开始
Okay. Okay,from the top.
开拍
And,action.
我很讶异你会同意跟我共用午餐
So I'm surprised you agreed to have lunch with me.
我也很讶异  但我终究是来了
I'm surprised too. But yet,here I am.
停停
Cut! Cut!
你在搞什么
What, what are you doing?
我很气他  因为他跟我上过床之后
I'm very angry at him because he slept with me
却再也没打电话给我了
and never called me back.
我也是 还有我
Me too.  Me too!
冷静点  她是说在剧情里面
Calm down. She means on the show.
我们需要新的临时演员
We need some new extras around here.
哇  你已经到了
Wow. You're here already.
是的  艾玛跟我提早进来
Yes. Emma and I came in a little early
准备报告的相关资料
to do research on the presentation.
事实上  我做了一些修改
Actually,I made a few changes.
我觉得相关情况我已完全了解了
I think I'm caught up on everything.
随便问我一个问题吧
So ask me anything.
你要怎么调整椅子呢  除了这个
How do you fix the chair?  Except that!
嗨  泽纳先生
Hello,Mr. Zelner.
今天下午的报告  我们都已经准备好了
We are all ready for our presentation this afternoon.
很好  因为10分钟之后就要开始了
Good,because it's in 10 minutes.
什么  我做不到  我宝宝在这里
What? I can't do that. I have the baby.
罗斯一个小时之后才会来接她
Ross is not gonna pick her up for an hour.
那加文可以上台报告  好吗
Then Gavin can give the presentation, ok?
我们必须现在就开始
We have to do it now.
罗夫今天要提早走
Ralph needs to leave early today.
他要搭直升机去购物
He's going helicopter shopping.
顺你的意了  你赢了  你赢了
Well,there you go,you win. You win.
你可以上台报告  让他们爱死你
You get to do the presentation. You'll knock them dead.
没有人会记得我在这里工作过
No one will remember that I worked here,
然后罗夫会搭上直升机
and then Ralph will buy his helicopter..
而超级加文会跟他一起飞
and Super Gavin will just fly right alongside of him.
你可以上台去做报告
You can do the presentation.
不  我不行  我宝宝在这里
No,I can't. I have a baby.
我会看着她
I'll watch her.
你为什么要这样
Why would you do that?
因为你工作很认真  而这是你的工作
Because you worked really hard, and it's your job.
而且你有点疯狂
And you're a little crazy.
你真的很好
That's really nice.
我应该告诉你
I should tell you that
哭泣的女人让我觉得很不自在
crying women make me very uncomfortable.
那你可能不会喜欢接下来要发生的事
Well,you're not gonna like what's coming.
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm sorry,I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
天呐
God.
谢谢你  谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you.
我没事的  别担心
I'm really fine. Don't worry.
我很会带小孩的
I'm great with children.
我是加文·米奇  很高兴认识你
Gavin Mitchell. Pleased to meet you.
请不要开除我的朋友
Please don't fire my friend.
让我先跟她谈谈
Just let me talk to her.
好吧  但是这是她最后一次机会
Okay,but this is her last chance.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you.Thank you.
我帮你一个忙如何
How about I do something for you?
明天  我帮你带一顶帽子
Tomorrow,I'll bring you a hat,
让你遮住秃头
cover up the bald.
听着  菲比  我刚跟导演谈完
Listen,Phoebe. I was just talking to the director..
他说  或许  这一次你不要打德雷克
and he was thinking maybe this time you don't hit Drake.
你只要端盘子就可以了
You just wait on the tables.
我做不到
I can't do that.
我是演员  我有原则的
I'm an actor. I have a process.
你是按摩师  你有张挖了个洞的桌子
You're a masseuse. You have a table with a hole in it.
等等  我知道这是怎么回事了
Wait,I see what's happening here.
你感到威胁了
You're threatened.
什么
What?
我的演技太好  抢了你的风头
I'm so good in the scene that I'm stealing focus from you.
接受挑战吧  崔比安尼
Rise to the challenge,Tribbiani,
因为我提高了擂台标准
because I just raised the bar.
提升自己  向我看齐吧
Come join me up here.
你可以开除她  但是最好叫警卫过来
Yeah,you can fire her,but I would call security.
她不会那么容易走的
She won't go easy.
你装的  你不可能装的
You faked it? You couldn't have faked it.
是可以的  只要装点表情跟声音
Yes,you can. You just make the faces and the noises.
男人可以装高潮吗
Guys can fake it?
难以置信  伪装高潮明明是女人的专利
Unbelievable. The one thing that's ours.
你为何要伪装高潮呢
Why would you fake it
我们是要生个小孩呀
when we're trying to have a baby?
那正是我要装的原因
Well,that's actually why.
听着  我正在换工作
Look,I'm starting a whole new career now.
我不是说我不想要孩子
I'm not saying I don't want a baby.
只是  或许我们可以等一阵子
I'm just saying maybe we could wait a little while.
一个月吗
Like a month?
或是一年
Or a year?
不是吧  你想要等一年
Really? You wanna wait a year?
或许等不到一年
It could be less than a year.
我是说  你知道我的能力
I mean,you've heard my stuff.
"裤子  跟内裤一样  只是长一点"
"Pants. Like shorts but longer."
可能会不止一年吧
It'll probably be more than a year.
我真的很想生个孩子
I really wanna have a baby.
嗯  是啊  我也是
Well,yeah,me too.
听着  我回去做老本行好了
Look,I'll just get my old job back.
不  我要你做你热爱的工作
No,I want you to have a job that you love..
不是什么数据分析跟资料重组的
not statistical analysis and data reconfiguration.
我辞职后  你才了解我在做什么
I quit,and you learn what I do?
我觉得永远不会有
I think there's never gonna be
适合生小孩的完美时机
a right time to have a baby.
现在你失业了  但一阵子过后
Now you're unemployed,and in a little while..
你就会找到一份让你忙不过来的工作
you'll find a new job that'll keep you really busy.
总是会有理由不能生小孩的
There's always gonna be a reason not to do this..
但是我想  一旦有了孩子
but I think once the baby comes,
我们就会忘了这一切的理由
we'll forget about all those reasons.
我想也是
I guess.
我是说  有小孩总是很吓人的事
I mean,it's always gonna be scary when we have a baby.
真的会是很吓人的
It's gonna be really scary.
老天  等我们有了孩子
I mean,God,when we have a baby..
将会有许多事情超乎我们的掌控
there's gonna be so much that we're not able to control.
我是说  公寓将会一团乱
I mean,the apartment's gonna be a mess.
我会没有时间整理
I won't have time to clean it.
要是宝宝跑到缎带抽屉里
What if the baby gets into the ribbon drawer..
把所有的缎带都弄乱了呢
and messes up all the ribbons?
万一没有地方可以放缎带
What if there's no room for a ribbon drawer..
所有的空间都被宝宝的东西占满了呢
because the baby's stuff takes up all the space?
缎带要放哪呢
Where will all the ribbons go?
要不要在你改变主意前  赶快去受孕
Should we go make a baby before you change your mind?
是啊  快点  好的
Yes,please!  Okay.
而且我保证  这一次我不会装了
And I promise I will not fake it this time.
我希望我也可以说相同的话
Well,I wish I could say the same.
我仍有点战栗
I'm a little shook up.
我知道你故意导致手术失败的
I know you botched that operation on purpose.
我现在还没有办法证明
I can't prove it yet,
但等我拿到证据
but when I do,
你会因谋杀而坐牢的
you'll be going to jail for murder.
我不在乎你是不是我弟弟
I don't care if you are my brother.
我不是你弟弟
I'm not your brother.
我的孩子怎么办呢  德雷克
What about my children,Drake?
不  不  不
No! No! No!
天啊
God!